Well,that thing's clearly in the way.
這個顯然沒用
All right.
Damn fridge!
死冰箱
-Hi,Joey. How you doing? -Great...
-喬伊，你好嗎？ -很好
roomie.
室友
-I guess we are roommates. -I know.
-我們現在的確是室友 -沒錯
Now that you bring it up, our fridge is broken.
經你一提， 我們的冰箱壞了
We need a new one.
得買台新的
I checked and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
我打聽過，你得出4百 感激不盡
I'm not paying for that.
我才不跟你分
I'm just here while they fix my place.
我只住到我們那邊整理好
Look, Rach, my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
瑞秋，這台冰箱是我出生之後 我父母買的
I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
我用都沒問題 你一來它就壞了
What does that tell you?
這意味著什麼？
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
冰箱無法和人一樣長壽
You know the ATM only lets you take out 300, so...
好，你也知道自動提款機 一次只能提3百
I'll take a check for the rest.
剩下的1百我就收支票
You're joking, right?
你在開玩笑吧？
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
那當然，我不收支票
Thank God, you're pretty.
幸好你很帥
The One With Joey's Fridge
本集播出：「羅斯的煩惱」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hi! Do you guys know any cute guys?
你們有認識的帥哥嗎？
Of course. My good friend Joey over here.
當然有 就是我的好朋友喬伊
I'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
我忘了…謝謝你
There's a charity ball and Ralph Lauren has a table...
週末有大型慈善晚會 羅夫羅蘭買了一桌
so I have to go.
我也得去
-What charity? -I don't know.
為什麼兌款？ 不曉得
Something,either trees or disease...
不是某種樹就是某種病…
Ralph mumbles a lot.
羅夫很會碎碎念
-He mumbles when you're not attentive? -Yeah. It's weird.
-羅夫都趁你不專心時碎碎念嗎 -對呀，好奇怪
But I need to find a date.
總之我得找個男伴
What kind of date?
你想找什麼樣的人？
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
自己有晚禮服或租得起晚禮服
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
所以身家起碼要有50元
So close.
只差一點
-Hey,everybody! -Hi,there.
大家好
-This is Elizabeth. -Hi,Elizabeth.
這是伊麗莎白
I'm the student.
我就是那個學生
Isn't she cute? Nope.
真可愛…才怪
Weren't you guys supposed to...
也許我不該多嘴
not be seen together?
但你們在一起不是不能被看到
We aren't.
我們沒有在一起
We just happen to have run into each other here.
沒有，我們只是兩個 在咖啡館巧遇的人
This is...
Oh,sly!
真奸詐
I wanted to meet you guys, but I have to run.
我很想多認識你們 但是我得走了
-See you later? -Okay.
改天見 好
-Bye, Ross. -Bye. See you.
-羅斯再見 -再見
-Didn't mean to run into you,sir. -That's quite all right,ma'am.
老師，我不是故意撞到你的 沒關係
Bye.
Why is she leaving? Is it a school night and she has homework?
她為什麼要走？ 剛放學功課一大堆？
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
對，她明天要交 分子流行病學報告
Tell her good luck with that.
幫我祝她好運
Anyone else? Bring them on.
還有嗎？別客氣
-When's her birthday? -I don't know. Why?
她什麼時候生日？ 我不知道，怎麼了？
It's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
我好久沒吃兒童生日餐了
-I like Elizabeth. -Well,thanks.
我喜歡伊麗莎白 謝謝
I like her so much, tell her I want my cookies early this year.
我真的很喜歡她 叫她今年早點送女童子軍餅乾來
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
我要薄荷巧克力餅和巧克力派
Give him a break. Ross, how's it going with her?
你們別鬧他了 說真的，你們交往得怎樣？
It's been great.
非常好
She's 20, so she's not too serious, which is perfect for me now.
她才20歲，還不想太認真 最適合現在的我
That's great. Seriously, she seems nice.
太好了，她真的好像很不錯
I know you guys like to give me a hard time...
謝謝，我知道你們喜歡臭我
but it means a lot to me.
但我真的很希望你們能喜歡她
-Just knowing.. -Okay,I got a good one.
只要知道你們… 我想到一個很棒的
What is she,like,12?
好，她是才12歲嗎？
Chandler, do we talk about our relationship enough?
錢德，你覺得我們的溝通夠嗎
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll-Ups?
夠，有水果卷嗎？
Okay.
I thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
我剛想到一個人 很適合當瑞秋的男伴
That's so funny. We found someone too.
有意思，我們也找到人了
Good. She'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
那好，她可以在我的人 和你們的怪胎之中選一個
-Why would our guy be a weirdo? -Because that's just your taste.
-為什麼我們的人是怪胎？ -你們的品味就是那樣
See, Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
瑞秋才不會選你的蠢人
-Yeah? -Yeah.
是嗎？ 沒錯
My guy is a lawyer, who does volunteer work.
我這個是律師，還當義工
And he has one of these.
而且他有這個東西
A face ass?
臉屁股？
A chin dimple.
下巴窩啦
Well,you know,our guy works with Chandler.
我們這個是錢德的同事
He's really nice and smart, and he's a great dresser.
人好聰明又會打扮
-Have you seen your guy's body? -No. Our guy's just a floating head.
你們看過他的身體嗎？ 沒有，他是一顆飄來飄去的頭
Well,my guy is spectacular. He's a massage client.
我這個身材很贊 他是我的客人
And one time, when he was on the table, I looked at it. And I mean all of it.
有一次他在按摩台上 就被我看光光了
-You're not supposed to look. -Like there are police for that.
你不能偷看 警察又不會抓
You look? You massaged me.
你會偷看？我給你按摩過
I know.
沒錯
Fine. Your guy may have a great body, but our guy is really funny.
好，你那個或許身材很好 但我們這個很風趣
Chandler funny?
錢德式的風趣？
-Our guy's a great dancer. -My guy's well-read.
我們這個舞功高強 我這個飽讀詩書
-Our guy has great hair. -My guy has great teeth.
我們這個髮質很好 我這個牙齒漂亮
Our guy smells incredible.
我們這個香得不得了
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
你真這麼哈他？
Well,you don't look good, Joe.
你的臉色不太好
The fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
冰箱壞了，我得把東西都吃掉
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
冷盤、冰淇淋、萊姆…
What was in that brown jar?
咖啡色罐子裡是什麼？
-That's still in there? -Not anymore.
那個還在？ 現在不在了
So anyway,how do you want to pay me?
總之你要怎麼付錢給我？
Is this a service you're providing me?
你要提供某種服務嗎？
No,for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
不是，是我要買冰箱 我們要買冰箱
Our new fridge?
我們？
-I don't live here anymore. -So what?
我已經不住這裡了 那又怎樣？
Look,okay,suppose we were a divorced couple.
假設我們是離婚夫妻
And I got custody of the kid. Right?
我取得孩子的監護權
Now suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
結果孩子死了 我總得買個新孩子
Okay.
好
Give me $400!
給我4百元
Thank God, you're pretty.
幸好你很帥
Professor Geller?
蓋勒教授
Oh,a student I don't know.
一名我不認識的學生
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
能不能跟您談一下？
Yes,of course. What would this be regarding?
當然可以，是哪方面的事？
Making out in your office.
在你的研究室親熱
Of course. Why don't we go inside.
好，我們進去再說
-What? -Doorknob.
怎麼了？ 門把
Sorry.
抱歉
I actually do need to talk to you.
我真的有事要講
What about?
好，什麼事？
-Spring vacation? -Spring vacation?
-春假的事 -春假的事？
Yeah, we have time off, and a lot of people are going on trips..
對，學校沒課 很多人要去旅行…
-Professor Geller. -Yes,Professor Friesenstinlender.
-蓋勒教授 -是，菲森死盯個樂教授…
I'll be with you in one moment.
我馬上就好
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
那我就買一盒薄荷巧克力餅
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
你們不懂 伊麗莎白想找我跟她去旅行
Is that taking it slow? I'm not ready for this.
這樣叫慢慢來嗎？ 我還沒準備好
-What do I tell her? -Tell her the truth,tell her you're not ready.
-我該怎麼說？ -實話實說，說你還沒準備好
I could do that.
可以試試
-What if she gets upset? -Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
要是她不高興呢？ 你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
Or you could just, you know, you...
或者你也可以…
What the hell are you doing?
你幹什麼？
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
我幹什麼？你弄壞我的冰箱
What? How do..?
什麼？你怎麼...
How do you know it's even broken?
你怎麼知道它壞了？
You think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
它怎麼壞的我會不知道嗎？
Excuse me!
你等一下
Well,what do you know?
看吧
Broken!
壞了
That'll be $400.
請賠4百
Joey, I saw you push him.
喬伊，我看見你推他了
You pushed him.
是你推的
Joey,I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
喬伊，我沒把它弄壞 它已經壞一陣子了
Remember I told you about our fridge?
我不是提過我們的冰箱的事？
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
我還沒拿到你該出的錢
Do not give him any money!
不要給他錢
I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
你少插嘴，你撞壞我的冰箱
-You wanted to see me,Professor Geller? -Yes. Please come in.
-蓋勒教授，你找我？ -是的，請進
-Doorknob? -Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
-門把？ -對，你有點玩上癮了
I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.
我想繼續上次春假的話題
Good.
好
Look,I...
聽我說，我…
Look,I'm having a great time with you.
我跟你在一起很開心
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
我不想進展得太快 或是給我們太多壓力
So I'm sorry, I just don't think we should go away together yet.
所以很抱歉 我們還不能一起旅行
It's too soon.
太快了
Ross,I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
羅斯，你誤會我的意思了
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
我只是想告訴你 我要去佛羅里達2星期
No.
不
I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
是你誤會我的意思了
What I meant was..
我的意思是…
You are so adorable.
你好可愛
That. Let's talk about that.
這個，我們來討論這個
-Hi. -Hi.
How did it go with Elizabeth?
你跟伊麗莎白談得怎樣？
Fine. Just a misunderstanding. She didn't want me to go with her.
沒事，只是一場誤會 她沒有要找我去
She just wanted to let me know she's going to Florida for a spring vacation.
她只是要告訴我她要去放春假
Wait a minute. Is she going for spring vacation or spring break? Wahoo!
等等，她是去放春假 還是去春遊？
What's the difference?
有什麼差別？
Spring vacation, you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
春假是跟爺爺奶奶共享天倫
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
春遊是跟兄弟會的人上床
You know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
並非每個人的春遊都那樣
-What did you do on yours? -I went to Egypt with my dad.
你做了什麼？ 我跟我爸去埃及
I can see it now. "Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx,wahoo!"
我可以想像 「爸，是人面獅身像」
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than: "Spring break,wahoo!"
伊麗莎白那麼正經 不會去「春遊」
Come on, she's taking my class.
好嗎？她修了我的課
-And slept with the professor. -I'm gonna call her.
-還跟教授上床 -我去打給她
You guys, I want you to meet Sebastian.
各位，這是賽巴斯欽
We met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream.
我們剛剛在報攤認識 我們都買了「原野與河流」
What? I read that.
我有在看啊
-Can I get you a cup of coffee? -Yes. Thank you.
你要咖啡嗎？ 要，謝謝
-Rachel, what the hell is this? -What?
瑞秋，你這是什麼意思？
You ask us to find a guy, and you come traipsing in here with a guy of your own?
什麼？ 你叫我們幫你找人 卻自己帶了個人來
You found me a guy?
你們幫我找到人了？
Yes. We found you a really cute, funny guy from Chandler's work.
對，我們在錢德的公司 相中一個可愛風趣的人
Yeah,and I found you one too, who is not a weirdo.
我也找了一個不是怪胎的人
You know what though, guys, I really appreciate that...
你們知道嗎？真是謝謝你們
but I'm gonna take Sebastian.
不過我帶賽巴斯欽去就好了
Are you sure? Our guy smells incredible.
你確定？我們這個很香喔
Would you stop it with that already?
別再提那個了好嗎？
-Here you go. -Thank you.
-你的咖啡 -謝謝
So, Sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?
賽巴斯欽，你有在當義工嗎？
-Not really. Why? -No reason.
沒有，怎麼了？
I know a single guy who does care about other people.
沒事，我只是認識一個 關心別人的單身漢
Are you funny?
你風趣嗎？
-Excuse me? -What are you guys doing?
-什麼？ -你們在幹什麼？
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
你風趣嗎？講個笑話來聽
I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
Well,so do a lot of people.
很多人都想
-Actually,I gotta get going. -But you..
說實話我該走了
-Give me a call sometime. -You didn't give me your phone number.
-有空打電話給我 -你沒給我電話號碼
Okay,see you later.
好，那就改天見
Turns out he is kind of funny.
原來他蠻風趣的
I cannot believe you guys!
你們真是太扯了
He was really nice, and he just left because of you!
他人很好，卻被你們趕走了
Yeah, but "Sebastian"? What is that, a cat's name?
賽巴斯欽耶？ 那是貓的名字嗎？
You know what I noticed, Rachel? He scares easy.
你知道我發現什麼？ 他很容易被嚇到
Is that the kind of guy you wanna take to a ball?
你想帶這種人參加舞會嗎？
"Hey,Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
「賽巴斯欽，要不要跳舞？」
"Okay. I gotta go."
「好，我得走了」
Stop it. Rachel,we're very sorry.
別再說了 瑞秋，對不起
That is a very insensitive thing to do.
我們太過份了
Let us make it up to you. We have two really great guys for you.
這樣吧，讓我們補償你 我們有兩個好男人讓你挑
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
對啊，你有什麼損失？
You might even end up with someone really special. If you pick my guy.
搞不好會認識讓你心動的人 如果你選我這邊的話
-All right. -So you will meet our guys?
好吧 你願意見我們找的人？
Yes.
我願意
It doesn't matter which one you choose. It's up to you.
你要選誰都行，由你自己決定
Our guy is perfect.
我們這個很完美
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed not good enough for herself.
或者你也可以選 菲比自己看不上眼的人
There you are! You broke my fridge.
菲比，你在這裡 你弄壞我的冰箱
You owe me $400.
欠我4百
-Okay,sure. -Really?
好吧 真的？
Technically,you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...
技術上來說你欠我6百
on your last 10 auditions.
你最近十次試鏡我都有祝禱
Call it even?
那就扯平了？
Okay.
好吧
There you are.
回來了
What did Elizabeth say?
伊麗莎白怎麼說？
Turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break,wahoo."
她真的是要去德通納春遊
That means wet T-shirt contests, guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
也就是有濕T恤美女選拔賽 男生朝女生身上扔水球
waking up with strangers.
在陌生人身邊醒來
She is gonna have a great time!
她會玩得很爽
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
她要住可樂娜飯店嗎？
-You know the hotels? -I was there! Spring Break '81,wahoo!
-你熟那裡的飯店？ -當然，我參加過81年春遊
In 1981,you were 13.
81年你才13歲
So? I drove down, sold T-shirts. Had a blast.
那又怎樣？我開車去賣T恤 玩得好開心
You know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
你們知道誰最會瘋？ 酒醉的大學女生
Okay,she can't go.
好，她不准去
You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
羅斯，你不能叫她不要去 你們才交往沒多久
-What am I supposed to do? -You just have to be cool with it.
-那我該怎麼辦？ -不怎麼辦，你只能接受
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢？
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
那這次你就別娶她
I'm sorry, this is very serious. And you know what,Ross?
對不起，這是很嚴肅的事 你知道嗎？
You like her, she likes you, everything's gonna be fine.
你喜歡她 她也喜歡你，不會有事的
You're right. I'm probably overreacting.
你說得對，我反應過度了
It's just she's staying at this party hotel on the beach...
她要住在濱海飯店
with a huge pool and free drinks with every meal.
有大游泳池，每頓都吃大餐…
If she's got enough money for that, she can certainly pat for the fridge she broke.
她既然這麼有錢 一定能賠償她弄壞的冰箱
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.
你能去旅行真是好事
I've been working so hard this semester.
就是啊，我這學期那麼用功
I really need to go crazy, blow off some steam.
很需要瘋狂一下，緩解壓力
Sure.
當然
Look,I don't know if your plans are finalized yet,but...
我不知道你的計劃已定了沒
I know a great way to blow off steam.
還有一個辦法可以緩解壓力
-What? -Are you into crafts at all?
-什麼辦法？ -你喜歡做手工藝嗎？
Ross,are you okay?
羅斯，你還好嗎？
Yeah. Of course I'm okay.
我當然很好
I'm just being supportive.
我只是在表示支持
Supportive of you and this whole trip...
支持你和這次旅行
and what's this?
還有這是什麼？
It's a bathing suit?
那是泳衣
To wear in front of people?
你要穿它去見人？
Is that supportive?
這樣叫支持嗎？
Is this?
這樣是嗎？
Okay,good.
太好了
-Hey. -Hi.
We're so glad you decided to meet our guy. You'll like him so much.
很高興你答應見我們找的人 你一定會很喜歡他
-When do you want to meet him? -I don't know.
-你要什麼時候見他？ -不曉得
-I don't work late tomorrow night. -Tomorrow night is good.
-我知道我明天不用加班 -明天不錯…
But why put off something till tomorrow that you could do it right now?
不過現在能做的事 為什麼要拖到明天？
-Eldad,come here! -What?
艾達，過來
-This is Rachel. -How are you?
艾達，這位是瑞秋 你好嗎？
A little blindsided but good.
有點措手不及，不過我很好
Eldad,sit down. Move over now.
艾達，坐…你坐過去
There you go. There you are.
這就對了
Okay,we can take a hint!
好，我們知道了
What? What are you doing here?
你來幹什麼？
This is Patrick.
這位是派屈克
-Hi. -Hi.
You're too late because she's already with our guy.
你來晚了 她跟我們那個在一起了
You're right,I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
天哪，我是來晚了 他們正坐在沙發上聊天
Come on.
Rachel? This is Patrick.
瑞秋 怎樣？ 這是派屈克
-Hi. -Hi.
This is the guy I was telling you about.
他就是我說的那個人
This suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
相信我，這套西裝 太委屈底下的身材了
Okay.
好
But, Phoebe, I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
但是 菲比 我現在有點事
Okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
好，沒關係，你坐
-You can't do that! -I should go.
你不能這樣 我走好了
Sit down, we're winning.
坐下，我們佔上風
Maybe I should go.
也許我才應該走
No. Have a seat!
不要，坐下
Rachel, you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
瑞秋，你還沒摸過艾達的頭髮
-He has the softest hair. Touch it. -I'm good.
超柔順的，你摸摸看 不必了
Rachel, Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
瑞秋，派屈克很有錢 拿錢給她
This isn't really worth the free massage.
這個免費按摩的代價太高了
-That's right. Bye-bye. -No.
沒錯，派屈克，再見
Eldad is much more cooperative, and he can dance.
艾達合作多了，而且很會跳舞
You dance for Rachel.
你跳舞給瑞秋看
Don't dance for me. Please!
不，拜託不要
What is the matter with you?
你們是怎麼搞的？
Yeah, let's talk it out.
沒錯，大家來說清楚 我…
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
只有我覺得尷尬嗎？
I'm a little embarrassed.
我也有點尷尬
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys.
該尷尬的是你們 這實在是太扯了
I do not need you to get me a date.
很謝謝你們 但我不需要你們幫我找人
-Why did she ask us to..? -I am still talking!
-那你為什麼叫我們… -我還沒說完
Then you chase away the one guy I actually liked.
你們還把我真正喜歡的人趕走
No offense to you guys. Really, congratulations on...
我沒有冒犯的意思，真的 恭喜你...
all the cash.
有那麼多現金
And you really do have very soft hair.
還有你…你的頭髮真的很柔順
But I'd much rather go to the ball by myself than go through any more of this.
但我寧可自己參加晚會 也不要再受這種氣
Goodbye.
再見
Now,do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
你有用什麼特別的潤發乳嗎？
Papaya extract.
有，木瓜粹取液
Thank you.
謝謝
So have a great time down there.
好好去玩吧
-I will. -Yeah.
我會的
-Did you pack that bathing suit? -Yeah.
你有帶那套泳衣嗎？ 有
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while.
我剛才把它藏起來 實在蠻好笑的
Anyway.
總之…
I am worried about that suit.
我不是擔心那套泳裝太曝露
Not because it's revealing, which I'm fine with.
這一點我不在意
I'm concerned about your health.
我是關心你的健康
Sun exposure.
怕你曬到
Don't worry,I have plenty of sun block.
放心，我帶了一大堆防曬油
-It's SPF 30. -All right.
防曬係數30
Well, if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
如果真的有30就好了
Sometimes you get 30, sometimes it's 4 and...
有時候是30，有時候只有4
more often than not,it's just milk.
我發誓有很多都只是牛奶
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
羅斯，你放心
I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
I really like you.
我很喜歡你
I like how things are going between us.
我喜歡我們的關係
-Really? -Yeah.
真的？ 對
I'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
我只是跟朋友們去玩一玩
Okay. Cool.
好吧
Here they are!
他們來了 伊麗莎白
Call me!
打電話給我
Sorry for pushing those guys on you.
瑞秋，抱歉把那些人硬塞給你
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
沒關係，結果我玩得很開心
The charity was a big success, and they raised a lot of money and awareness.
晚會很成功 兌到很多款，引起很多重視
So, what was it for anyway?
它是為什麼兌款？
I wanna say a disease.
我很想說是一種疾病
I just got this really weird message from Ross. He said to turn on MTV.
羅斯留了奇怪的留言 叫我們看MTV台
Oh,my God,look! That's Elizabeth!
看，是伊麗莎白
Professor Geller.
蓋勒教授
To be 13 again....
重溫舊夢 是啊